[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "And when it came to the actual moment of capture and arrest, did you actually see that happening?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "it", "came", "to", "the", "actual", "moment", "of", "capture", "and", "arrest", ",", "did", "you", "actually", "see", "that", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "How are you feeling now it's all over?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "feeling", "now", "it", "'s", "all", "over", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "It's been a horrendous week because in many different ways, all of us have experienced the horror of the bombing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "a", "horrendous", "week", "because", "in", "many", "different", "ways", ",", "all", "of", "us", "have", "experienced", "the", "horror", "of", "the", "bombing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Elizabeth, what do we know about the injuries he may have sustained?", "question_tokens": ["Elizabeth", ",", "what", "do", "we", "know", "about", "the", "injuries", "he", "may", "have", "sustained", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "You know, we don't know much about the injuries, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "much", "about", "the", "injuries", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Can you hear me, Susan?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "hear", "me", ",", "Susan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Susan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What was that like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "I think we were all just really on edge, really nervous about what was going to happen next.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "were", "all", "just", "really", "on", "edge", ",", "really", "nervous", "about", "what", "was", "going", "to", "happen", "next", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "What did you think about, learning that he was living here or at least hiding out here during the last 24 hours?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "about", ",", "learning", "that", "he", "was", "living", "here", "or", "at", "least", "hiding", "out", "here", "during", "the", "last", "24", "hours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "IN", "JJS", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "It was terrifying.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "terrifying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "How does Boston come back?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "Boston", "come", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Oh, geez.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "geez", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "What would you like to see?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", "to", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Well, it's been a harrowing time for us and I'm sure for the victims' families and friends who have been spending a long week wondering where he's at.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "been", "a", "harrowing", "time", "for", "us", "and", "I", "'m", "sure", "for", "the", "victims", "'", "families", "and", "friends", "who", "have", "been", "spending", "a", "long", "week", "wondering", "where", "he", "'s", "at", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Was it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Let me ask you about that, Juliette Kayyem, because that could be a big question mark once the celebration of this particular operation which has clearly been successful, once that dies down, there will be an inquest into what has gone on in the background to all this, and it has turned out the FBI did indeed interview one of these two brothers two years ago and he is somebody that they now believe was having quite serious Islamic fundamentalist development in his life, will there be raised eyebrows about this?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "about", "that", ",", "Juliette", "Kayyem", ",", "because", "that", "could", "be", "a", "big", "question", "mark", "once", "the", "celebration", "of", "this", "particular", "operation", "which", "has", "clearly", "been", "successful", ",", "once", "that", "dies", "down", ",", "there", "will", "be", "an", "inquest", "into", "what", "has", "gone", "on", "in", "the", "background", "to", "all", "this", ",", "and", "it", "has", "turned", "out", "the", "FBI", "did", "indeed", "interview", "one", "of", "these", "two", "brothers", "two", "years", "ago", "and", "he", "is", "somebody", "that", "they", "now", "believe", "was", "having", "quite", "serious", "Islamic", "fundamentalist", "development", "in", "his", "life", ",", "will", "there", "be", "raised", "eyebrows", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "There probably will.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "probably", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"], "PERSON": ["Juliette Kayyem"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "How are you feeling personally about the way this has all played out tonight?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "feeling", "personally", "about", "the", "way", "this", "has", "all", "played", "out", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Well, I'm feeling good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "feeling", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "This has been a successful operation by the FBI, hasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "has", "been", "a", "successful", "operation", "by", "the", "FBI", ",", "has", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Yes, it has been, by all law enforcement.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "has", "been", ",", "by", "all", "law", "enforcement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "What is going to happen now procedurally that they've got him under arrest and have him alive?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "to", "happen", "now", "procedurally", "that", "they", "'ve", "got", "him", "under", "arrest", "and", "have", "him", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "JJS", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "There are two big questions right away.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "two", "big", "questions", "right", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, how will that play out, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Alan", "Dershowitz", ",", "how", "will", "that", "play", "out", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Well, he will get a fair trial.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "will", "get", "a", "fair", "trial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Governor?", "question_tokens": ["Governor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", ":", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Mayor Menino?", "question_tokens": ["Mayor", "Menino", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I just want to say very briefly -- thank you, thank you, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "want", "to", "say", "very", "briefly", "--", "thank", "you", ",", "thank", "you", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Menino"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Commissioner Davis?", "question_tokens": ["Commissioner", "Davis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Four days ago, my city was ruthlessly attacked.", "answer_tokens": ["Four", "days", "ago", ",", "my", "city", "was", "ruthlessly", "attacked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Davis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Watertown Police Department"], "LOCATION": ["Watertown"]}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Watertown Police Chief Deveau?", "question_tokens": ["Watertown", "Police", "Chief", "Deveau", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "As the police chief of Watertown, I can't be prouder of my community and the men and women of the Watertown Police Department.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "the", "police", "chief", "of", "Watertown", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "be", "prouder", "of", "my", "community", "and", "the", "men", "and", "women", "of", "the", "Watertown", "Police", "Department", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Watertown Police Chief Deveau"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Chief, did you have communication with the suspect?", "question_tokens": ["Chief", ",", "did", "you", "have", "communication", "with", "the", "suspect", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Excuse me.", "answer_tokens": ["Excuse", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donohue"]}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "WP", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Chief MacMillan from the MBTA?", "question_tokens": ["Chief", "MacMillan", "from", "the", "MBTA", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "I just want to thank all those who sent their thoughts and prayers to Officer Donohue and his family.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "want", "to", "thank", "all", "those", "who", "sent", "their", "thoughts", "and", "prayers", "to", "Officer", "Donohue", "and", "his", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["MBTA"], "PERSON": ["MacMillan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"], "LOCATION": ["Watertown", "Boston"]}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "How did the events transpire at the boat?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "the", "events", "transpire", "at", "the", "boat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "There was a call that came in to the Watertown police, three Boston police officers along with state troopers and FBI agents responded to Franklin Street.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "was", "a", "call", "that", "came", "in", "to", "the", "Watertown", "police", ",", "three", "Boston", "police", "officers", "along", "with", "state", "troopers", "and", "FBI", "agents", "responded", "to", "Franklin", "Street", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Can you talk about the imperative of taking him alive?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "talk", "about", "the", "imperative", "of", "taking", "him", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "We always want to take all the suspects alive.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "always", "want", "to", "take", "all", "the", "suspects", "alive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "WP", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Can you talk about why you wanted to take him?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "talk", "about", "why", "you", "wanted", "to", "take", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "We always want to take somebody alive so we can find out what happened, why it happened, and we can hold them for justice.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "always", "want", "to", "take", "somebody", "alive", "so", "we", "can", "find", "out", "what", "happened", ",", "why", "it", "happened", ",", "and", "we", "can", "hold", "them", "for", "justice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Have they aided and abetted the suspect?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "they", "aided", "and", "abetted", "the", "suspect", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Actually, I don't have that information.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "that", "information", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "This is it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "I think based upon our investigation at this point in time, the citizens of the city of Boston and this area can be confident that the threat has been removed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "based", "upon", "our", "investigation", "at", "this", "point", "in", "time", ",", "the", "citizens", "of", "the", "city", "of", "Boston", "and", "this", "area", "can", "be", "confident", "that", "the", "threat", "has", "been", "removed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "What kind of condition is the suspect in?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "condition", "is", "the", "suspect", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Suspect is in serious condition at the hospital.", "answer_tokens": ["Suspect", "is", "in", "serious", "condition", "at", "the", "hospital", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["MIT"]}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "They didn't rob the 7-Eleven so how did you know they were there at the same time?", "question_tokens": ["They", "did", "n't", "rob", "the", "7-Eleven", "so", "how", "did", "you", "know", "they", "were", "there", "at", "the", "same", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CD", "RB", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "The suspects came to our attention after a vicious assassination of a police officer at MIT and a subsequent robbery that occurred where we got videotape from a gas station.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "suspects", "came", "to", "our", "attention", "after", "a", "vicious", "assassination", "of", "a", "police", "officer", "at", "MIT", "and", "a", "subsequent", "robbery", "that", "occurred", "where", "we", "got", "videotape", "from", "a", "gas", "station", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Was he shot by police officer?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "shot", "by", "police", "officer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "The man who found him at the boat said that he was covered with blood.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "man", "who", "found", "him", "at", "the", "boat", "said", "that", "he", "was", "covered", "with", "blood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "What do you know about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "know", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "My assessment of that particular incident is that he was assassinated in his cruiser.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "assessment", "of", "that", "particular", "incident", "is", "that", "he", "was", "assassinated", "in", "his", "cruiser", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Do you know what he was doing there?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "he", "was", "doing", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "He was responding to a call for a disturbance.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "responding", "to", "a", "call", "for", "a", "disturbance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Could they have been at risk?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "they", "have", "been", "at", "risk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "We certainly did not give an all-clear.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "certainly", "did", "not", "give", "an", "all-clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Did he have explosives with him when he was captured?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "have", "explosives", "with", "him", "when", "he", "was", "captured", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "There's no report of explosives with him at capture but I got to tell you, I was at the scene last night just after this incident occurred.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "report", "of", "explosives", "with", "him", "at", "capture", "but", "I", "got", "to", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "was", "at", "the", "scene", "last", "night", "just", "after", "this", "incident", "occurred", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "NN", "MD", ":", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Could you explain that for us?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "explain", "that", "for", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Actually, the United States attorney may -- the FBI may want to explain that.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "the", "United", "States", "attorney", "may", "--", "the", "FBI", "may", "want", "to", "explain", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "What was the question?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "There was no Miranda warning given, they were claiming a public safety exception.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "was", "no", "Miranda", "warning", "given", ",", "they", "were", "claiming", "a", "public", "safety", "exception", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "Could we get an explanation?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "we", "get", "an", "explanation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "There is a public safety exemption in cases of national security and potential charges involving acts of terrorism.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "a", "public", "safety", "exemption", "in", "cases", "of", "national", "security", "and", "potential", "charges", "involving", "acts", "of", "terrorism", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Will you seek the federal death penalty?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "seek", "the", "federal", "death", "penalty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "You know, what I indicated earlier is that this is still an active, an ongoing investigation.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "what", "I", "indicated", "earlier", "is", "that", "this", "is", "still", "an", "active", ",", "an", "ongoing", "investigation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "MD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "RB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Karen?", "question_tokens": ["Karen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Straight to the boat and then can or the colonel talk a little about what happened when you were on the scene.", "answer_tokens": ["Straight", "to", "the", "boat", "and", "then", "can", "or", "the", "colonel", "talk", "a", "little", "about", "what", "happened", "when", "you", "were", "on", "the", "scene", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Was the boat searched during the day on the perimeter?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "the", "boat", "searched", "during", "the", "day", "on", "the", "perimeter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Yes, it was outside the perimeter during the day.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "was", "outside", "the", "perimeter", "during", "the", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Is there a chance the suspect won't make it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "chance", "the", "suspect", "wo", "n't", "make", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "And the president, going back to Jessica Yellin -- do we know what time the president's due to speak?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "president", ",", "going", "back", "to", "Jessica", "Yellin", "--", "do", "we", "know", "what", "time", "the", "president", "'s", "due", "to", "speak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "Was supposed to speak already 15 minutes ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Was", "supposed", "to", "speak", "already", "15", "minutes", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jessica Yellin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "What did you make of what they've been saying and positioning the case from the start here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "what", "they", "'ve", "been", "saying", "and", "positioning", "the", "case", "from", "the", "start", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "Well, they're asserting that there is a public safety exception that allows them to question him and then potentially use the information -- use the statements against him.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'re", "asserting", "that", "there", "is", "a", "public", "safety", "exception", "that", "allows", "them", "to", "question", "him", "and", "then", "potentially", "use", "the", "information", "--", "use", "the", "statements", "against", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "Are they right?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "That's not at all clear.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "at", "all", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]